My  30F,  husbands,  25M
parents  are  refusing  to
speak  with  him  after
we  decided  to  hyphenate
our  last  names.
Any  advice?
Hello  all,  my  hubby
and  I  got  married
three  weeks  ago.
To  honor  my  grandpa
who  passed  away  a
few  weeks  before  the
wedding,  I  felt  that
I  didn't
want  to  lose  my
last  name.
Hubby  and  I  decided
on  a  hyphenated  last
name.
His  parents  found  out
and  are  absolutely  furious
with  him,  and  probably
with  me  too.
We  have  no  idea
what  exactly  they're  furious
about  the  hyphenation,  that
he's  changing  his  last
name.
They  won't  talk,  so
I  have  absolutely  no
clue.
It's  tearing  up  my
husband  so  much,  and
I  feel  terrible  because
I  didn't  realize  it
would  go  down  like
this.
But  I  also  feel
like  this  is  a
choice  for  our  new
family  to  make,  the
first  of  many  important
choices,  and  they  must
respect  that.
Just  looking  for  some
advice  on  what  to
do  and  how  to
help  my  husband  through
it.